Register of the New left collection, 1923-2004
Hoover Institution Archives
- San Francisco State University, 1968-1970
  - Progressive Labor Party, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 45: 7)
  - The Resistance, 1969 (Box-folder 45: 8)
  - Silent Majority against Revoliutionary Tactics, 1969 (Box-folder 45: 9)
  - Strike Daily (Box-folder 45: 10)
  - Strike Support Committee, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 45: 11)
  - Students for a Democratic Society (SDS), 1969 (Box-folder 45: 12)
  - Third World Liberation Front, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 45: 13)
- SANE, 1971 (Box-folder 45: 14)
- Santa Barbara oil spill, 1969 (Box-folder 45: 15)
- Scientists and Engineers for Social and Political Action (SESPA), 1972-1973 (Box-folder 45: 16)
- Seattle Liberation Front, 1970 (Box-folder 45: 17)
- Smith, Pvt. Billy Dean, 1972 (Box-folder 45: 18)
- Socialist Labor Party, 1969 (Box-folder 46: 1)
- Socialist Party of Washington/Northwest, 1988 (Box-folder 46: 2)
- Socialist Workers Party, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 46: 3)
- Soledad Brothers, 1970 (Box-folder 46: 4)
- Southern Conference Educational Fund, 1971 (Box-folder 46: 5)
- Spartacist League, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 46: 6)
- Stanford University, 1965-1983
  - General, 1965-1983 (Box-folder 46: 7-10)
  - General, 1965-1983 (Box-folder 47: 1-5)
  - General posters, 1970
    Scope and Contents note
    Includes 2 issues of Street Wall Journal, April 1970, and one anti-ROTC poster, 1970. See also issues of Street Wall Journal in Poster collection, US8110.
  - Anti-ROTC movement, 1969 (Box-folder 47: 6-7)
  - Applied Electronics Laboratory sit-in, 1969 (Box-folder 47: 8)
  - April 3rd Movement, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 48: 1-2)
  - Black Student Union, 1968--1970 (Box-folder 48: 3)
  - Clippings, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 48: 4)
  - Days of Concern, 1968 (Box-folder 48: 5)
  - Encina Sit-in, 1969 (Box-folder 48: 6)
  - Franklin, Bruce, 1967-1972 (Box-folder 48: 7)
  - Free Campus Movement, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 48: 8)
  - Hooverville/Reganville, 1982 (Box-folder 48: 9-10)
  - Stanford Workshops on Political and Social Issues (SWOPSI), 1972 (Box-folder 49: 1)
  - Street Wall Journal, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 49: 2)
  - Student radicalism, 1968-1972
    - Chaparral, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 49: 3)
    - Chicanismo, 1970 (Box-folder 49: 4)
    - Cross Currents, 1969 (Box-folder 49: 5)
    - Stanford Daily, 1969 (Box-folder 49: 6-8)
    - Stanford Daily, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 50: 1-5)
    - Stanford Daily, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 51: 1-5)
    - Stanford Observer, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 52: 1)
    - Miscellaneous serial issues, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 52: 2-4)
- Stanford Research Institute, 1969 (Box-folder 52: 5-6)
- Student Mobilization Committee, 1970 (Box-folder 52: 7-8)
- Student protests, 1962-1979
  - General, 1962-1979 (Box-folder 52: 9-10)
  - General, 1962-1979 (Box-folder 53: 1)
  - University of New Mexico, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 53: 2)
- Students for a Democratic Society (SDS), 1962-1973
  - General, 1962-1973 (Box-folder 53: 3-8)
  - General, 1962-1973 (Box-folder 54: 1-7)
  - General, 1962-1973 (Box-folder 55: 1-7)
  - General, 1962-1973 (Box-folder 56: 1-2)
  - Articles, 1966-1973 (Box-folder 56: 3)
  - Bay Area, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 56: 4)
  - Conventions, 1969-1970
    - 1969 (Box-folder 56: 5)
    - 1970 (Box-folder 56: 6)
  - Factory Leafleting Committee, 1968 (Box-folder 56: 7)
  - Labor Committee, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 56: 8)
  - New Left Notes, 1972 (Box-folder 57: 1)
  - Port Huron Statement, 1966 (Box-folder 57: 2)
  - Radical Education Project, 1964-1969 (Box-folder 57: 3-7)
  - Radical Education Project, 1964-1969 (Box-folder 58: 1-2)
  - Revolutionary Marxist Caucus, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 58: 3)
  - Southern Student Organizing Committee, 1966-1972 (Box-folder 58: 4)
  - Summer 1972 (Box-folder 58: 4)
  - Work-in, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 58: 6)
- Symbionese Liberation Army, 1974 (Box-folder 59: 1)
- "Top Secret" (from R.G. Benedict, University of Nevada), 1971-1973 (Box-folder 59: 2-6)
- Third World Liberation Front, 1969 (Box-folder 59: 7)
- TUPART Monthly Reports, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 59: 8)
- Underground film, 1975 (Box-folder 59: 9)
- Underground press directories, 1970 (Box-folder 59: 10)
- Underground Press Syndicate, 1970 (Box-folder 59: 11)
- United States imperialism, 1965-1971 (Box-folder 60: 1)
- University of California (Berkeley), 1961-1973
  - General, 1965-1972 (Box-folder 60: 2-6)
  - General, 1965-1972 (Box-folder 61: 1-2)
  - Free Speech Movement (FSM), 1964-1965 (Box-folder 61: 3-7)
  - Radical Student Union, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 62: 7)
  - Reserve Officers Training Corps (ROTC) and other protests, 1970 (Box-folder 62: 8)
  - SLATE, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 62: 9)
  - Strike, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 62: 10)
  - Student Committee for Agricultural Labor (SCAL), 1965 (Box-folder 63: 1)
  - Student Labor Action Project (SLAP), 1971 (Box-folder 63: 2)
  - Third World Liberation Front (TWLF), 1969 (Box-folder 63: 3-5)
- University of California (San Diego), 1970 (Box-folder 63: 6)
- University of California (Santa Barbara), 1970 (Box-folder 63: 7)
- University of Connecticut (Hartford), 1972 (Box-folder 63: 8)
- Urban guerrilla warfare tactics, 1970 (Box-folder 63: 9)
- Venceremos, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 63: 10-11)
- Venceremos Brigade, 1970 (Box-folder 63: 12-14)
- Veterans Stars & Stripes for Peace, 1965-1969 (Box-folder 63: 14)
- Vietnam Moratorium, 1970 (Box-folder 64: 1)
- Vietnam Peace Parade Committee, 1970 (Box-folder 64: 2)
- Vietnam Veterans Against the War, 1971 (Box-folder 64: 3)
- Vietnam War and anti-war movement, 1965-1963 (Box-folder 64: 4-10)
- Vietnam War and anti-war movement, 1965-1973 (Box-folder 65: 1-7)
- Vietnam War and anti-war movement, 1965-1973 (Box-folder 66: 1-7)
- Vietnam War and anti-war movement, 1965-1973 (Box-folder 67: 1-4)
- War Resisters League, 1976 (Box-folder 67: 5)
- Weathermen (Weather Underground), 1971 (Box-folder 67: 6)
- W.E.B. DuBois Clubs, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 67: 7)
- White Panther Party, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 67: 8)
- Women's History Library, 1971 (Box-folder 67: 9)
- Women's International League for Peace and Freedom, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 67: 10)
- Women's liberation, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 67: 11)
- Women's liberation, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 68: 1-4)
- Worker-Student Alliance, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 68: 5)
- Worker student strikes, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 68: 6)
- Workers Action Movement, 1972 (Box-folder 68: 7)
- Wounded Knee, 1973 (Box-folder 68: 8)
- Young Americans for Freedom (YAF), 1969-1970 (Box-folder 68: 9)
- Young Lords, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 68: 10)
- Young People's Socialist League, 1969 (Box-folder 68: 11)
- Young Socialist Alliance, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 68: 12)
- Young Socialist Alliance, 1969 (Box-folder 69: 1)
- Young Workers Liberation League (CPUSA youth group), 1970 (Box-folder 69: 2)
- Youth Against War and Fascism, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 69: 3)
- Youth International Party (Yippies), 1969-1971 (Box-folder 69: 4)
- Zappa, Frank, 1985 (Box-folder 69: 5)
- Zippies, 1972 (Box-folder 69: 6)
- One microfilm reel of San Francisco State University newspapers, 1968-1969 (Microfilm-cabinet 1 reel)
- Photographs: 7 prints depicting protests at Stanford University, 1970 (Photo-file Envelope A)
- Incremental Materials, 1967-2004
  - Miscellaneous leaflets, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 69: 7-8)
  - Miscellaneous pamphlets, 1970-2004 (Box-folder 69: 9)
  - Guerrilla (Box-folder 69: 10)
  - Progressive Labor Party, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 69: 11)
  - Protest against George W. Bush, 2001 (Box-folder 69: 12)
  - Spartacist League, 1987-2001 (Box-folder 69: 13)
  - Stanford University, 1969-1998
    - Clippings, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 70: 1-4)
    - Leaflets, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 70: 5-6)
    - Thesis on Bruce Franklin case, 1998 (Box-folder 70: 7)
  - Oversize materials, 1964-1999
    - Amadou Diallo protest banner, 1999 (Box-folder 71: 1)
    - Amadou Diallo protest button, 1999 (Box-folder 71: 2)
    - Crisis at Columbia, 1968 (Box-folder 71: 3)
    - "Father and Sons" videorecording (VHS) by Don Lenzer, 1969 (Box-folder 71: 4)
    - Free Speech Movement songs (records), 1964 (Box-folder 71: 5)
    - Serial issues, 1963-1991
      - Miscellaneous, 1968-1979 (Box-folder 72: 1)
      - Rebel Worker and Up against the Bulkhead, 1970-1979 (Box-folder 72: 2)
      - Solidarity and Touch, 1971-1977 (Box-folder 72: 3)
      - Sedition and Willamette Bridge, 1970-1976 (Box-folder 73: 1)
      - New American Movement and miscellaneous, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 73: 2)
      - On the Road, Resistance News, and Survivalist, 1971-1987 (Box-folder 73: 3)
      - 12th Street Rag, First Amendment, and Sunday Ramparts, 1963-1971 (Box-folder 74: 1)
      - Strike Bulletin, UAW Unity, Workers World, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 74: 2)
      - Union W.A.G.E., 1972-1975 (Box-folder 74: 3)
      - Second Page, Task Force, and Toy Sun, 1968-1976 (Box-folder 74: 4)
      - People's Voice, Southern Patriot, Wildcat, and Women's Page, 1969-1986 (Box-folder 74: 5)
      - Torch, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 75: 1)
      - From out of Sherwood Forest and New Morning, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 75: 2)
      - North American Anarchist Review and Semper Fi, 1971-1991 (Box-folder 75: 3)
    - Miscellaneous flyers with woodblock illustrations, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 75: 4-5)
    - Miscellaneous serial issues, 1967-1972 (Box-folder 76: 1-5)
    - Oversize photographs depiciting protest scenes and counter-culture, 1970 (Box-folder 76: 6-12)
    - Posters and protest signs, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 76: 13-38)
    - Mask depicting Richard Nixon, 1972 (Box-folder 76: 39)
  - John Sinclair Freedom Rally sound recordings, 10 December 1971; 1.0 discs (Record-cabinet Record Cabinet)
    "Free John Now!" and "Prayer for John Sinclair" both jointly credited to Allen Ginsberg and Peter Orlovsky. Rainbow records catalog number 22191.